[
    {
        "question": "D3 on string 3",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "D#3 on string 3",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "E3 on string 3",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "F3 on string 3",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "F#3 on string 3",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "G3 on string 3",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "G#3 on string 3",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "A3 on string 3",
        "answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "A#3 on string 3",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "B3 on string 3",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "C4 on string 3",
        "answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "C#4 on string 3",
        "answer": "11"
    }	
]
